<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Dan Bennett</title>
    <description>The Brain Dump
</description>
    <link>http://dan-bennett.me/</link>
    <link href="http://dan-bennett.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:38:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Team Kryptk 24 Hour Charity Livestream - 16th &amp; 17th Jan 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The lovely folks over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.teamkryptk.com&quot;&gt;Team Kryptk&lt;/a&gt; are doing a 24 hour livestream in 2016 to raise money for &lt;strong&gt;MIND&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We have decided to choose “Mind” as our charity because as a group we all understand in our own ways the struggle with a mental health problem, be it through ourselves or our loved ones. We are hoping to raise awareness and promote the understanding through the improvement of services from your donations. Sometimes it is hard to understand something you aren’t personally going through, hopefully with just this little bit of difference our amazing community can do, we can help those going through mental health problems get advice and support they need. The aim is also to bring those who are unaware to reality of the lives of those around them and how to do their own part in helping them. Much like “Mind” we won’t give up until we can change the way people look at mental health problems and allow the progression of the support and respect of those who are going through it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please put this in your diary and support these guys and help raise money for an amazing charity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/team-kryptk-24-hour-charity-livestream</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/team-kryptk-24-hour-charity-livestream</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What I expect when I successfully run a Vim command</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But when I try a crazy key combination and successfully run a command this is what I expect to happen.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.michaellee.co/20151027-ken-shoryuken.png&quot; alt=&quot;vim&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have this exact same feeling. I’m getting a lot better at Vim than I used to. But when I try to work fast and do a bunch of little key commands, I find butter fingers gets the best of me and I just faff it all up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, it’s nicer to use than Nano… so it has that going for it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/what-i-expect-when-i-successfully-run-a-vim-command</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/what-i-expect-when-i-successfully-run-a-vim-command</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Note Taking as a Sysadmin</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;am-i-asking-too-much&quot;&gt;Am I asking too much?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my job, it’s vital that I take notes of things going on. Whether it’s work I’m doing or clients asking questions, notes are vital so that I can look back on them in the future in case something comes to bite me on the arse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the main thing. Backing myself up so that I can prove to myself or others that something was the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve mostly used Tomboy Notes. It’s a lovely little application that automatically generates a daily note to go throughout that day and I have a seperate note with my todo list, which is always massive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I’ve gotten into an issue where if I want to search for something, it’s difficult. Each day is seperate. In a different note. It just takes twice as long as it should to find stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A colleague of mine uses Amaya. It’s an old but useful application that creates pages that are XHTML based. He uses it for doing a year logbook. Which is the most perfect idea ever!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only issue, Amaya is old. It’s no longer being activtly developed and has some really stupidly annoying issues. So I need something modern…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;doesnt-anyone-care-anymore&quot;&gt;Doesn’t anyone care anymore?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people seem to be using Evernote or OneNote. I’ve tried both and I’ve hated them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OneNote I fell out of love with very quickly. It’s one of those apps that just never could sit right with me. It’s got some really stupid shortcut placements (Try inserting the current time or date…) and if the note is too big it just gets a bit slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same with Evernote. That is so slow and bulky. It’s also very slow to load and everytime I paste some text in it seems to have a massive hissy fit on where my cursor is and mostly shows me the advertisements at the bottom. Oh and constantly begs me to purchase Evernote Premium. Feck off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;simplicity-is-key&quot;&gt;Simplicity is key…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The great thing about Amaya is it’s HTML. It’s just one big HTML page which means I can easily CTRL + F and search for the words, date, time, month, foot I need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, because it doesn’t need anything fancy. It’s incredibly fast to use and viewing it is no hassle at all…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s still got some bulk to it for editing. I mean, it’s essentially a Microsoft FrontPage application, just a lot better and less arse. But it’s not made for note taking. It’s made for webpage development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;compromise&quot;&gt;Compromise&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve currently settled for another simple Jekyll installation. I’ve got a very simple look and feel to it. All it needs is to open the HTML file and display it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quotes from client emails are easily visible. I can easily link to things. I can easily insert code excerpts. It’s great. Because it’s all Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only downside with that, is I’m editing in Markdown. So I’m editing in a format that I cannot easily read as I can when reading the logbook itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a small compromise and with learning more about Markdown I’m sure I’d get used to it. But heck, why is there nothing that does this already?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;say-no-to-web-apps&quot;&gt;Say no to Web Apps!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web Apps are a big no no. I want something I have control over. Web Apps bug the living shit out of me. Always have, always will. If I want to use an &lt;em&gt;application&lt;/em&gt; I want to be able to have it in it’s own little thing doing it’s own little thing. I don’t want it relying on Google fecking Chrome just to run. Especially when Chrome uses enough RAM as it is…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-this-where-i-start-to-develop&quot;&gt;Is this where I start to develop?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I need to just accept that no one works the way I want to. Or at least, no one has thought of it. Maybe I’m unique in the way I want to record how I do things. Surely I can’t be alone? Can I?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it’s about time I stop whinging that there’s nothing and actually do something about it. Write a program that is universal, let’s me do the things I want to do and pleases my every need. How hard can it be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;does-everyone-write-markdown-in-plain-text&quot;&gt;Does everyone write Markdown in plain text?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s another thing. I’m writing all my logs in Plain Text. But with Markdown…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has no one written an application that lets you write in Markdown, but on the fly displays it as HTML? That way you’re typing away in Markdown and it’s showing it as HTML? How you expect it to look?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No buggy Preview panes, no &lt;code&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt; and double check everything’s grand. Just… show me how it’s meant to look as it’s typing. Please?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/rant&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/note-taking-as-a-sysadmin</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/note-taking-as-a-sysadmin</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iTunes should stay as one application...</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;not-separated-into-different-apps&quot;&gt;Not separated into different apps…&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iTunes is vast. You can listen to music, watch video, podcasts, movies, radio, stream, catch up on your latest artists… It’s all there in one big combined application. It’s one big thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though I understand why people say “iTunes should be separated into different apps”. But separating isn’t the answer. Redesigning is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;redesign&quot;&gt;Redesign!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest problem really is since Apple Music was introduced. It seems more of an after thought. As if, they designed Apple Music separately then whacked it into iTunes at last minute…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole music and video aspect of iTunes can easily be tidied up. &lt;em&gt;I say easily, I’m not a big designer I haven’t made a mock up.&lt;/em&gt; They should be integrated together so it’s seem less. Easy to use and with a simple opt in to benefit from the streaming part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iTunes Store and Apple Music also need integrated together. Find something you like? Buy it! Not sure? Keep streaming! &lt;em&gt;Or am I the only one that does this?&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Radio needs massively improved. Beats 1 needs to take centre stage with it clearly showing scheduled and past shows that can be &lt;em&gt;relistened&lt;/em&gt; to. Because boy oh boy that’s a faff and a half!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get why Apple Music came in and made people go &lt;em&gt;“WTF get this off my iTunes”&lt;/em&gt; but separating will just make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/itunes-should-stay-as-one</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/itunes-should-stay-as-one</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3D Touch on iOS 9</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;d-touch-is-amazing&quot;&gt;3D Touch is amazing.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s such a little addition but with such a big advantage for power users. It is essentially a &lt;em&gt;right click&lt;/em&gt; for the iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So many apps are implementing it well. Quick shortcuts to things within the app. However, I do feel Apple missed a trick out here …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apps can only interact for the user when they are open. This makes sense. But with 3D Touch, it would make sense if apps could show a modal window on screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, Tweetbot. If I 3D Touch on the app I get a shortcut to post a new tweet. Pressing this will load the app then take me to the New Tweet screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, surely this would be better if pressing New Tweet would just load up their own custom New Tweet modal window on the Home Screen. This way, you don’t leave the place you’re at and it goes away once you’ve sent that tweet. A great replacement for the - now missing - Post Tweet widget in the Notification Centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple, pls?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/3d-touch-ios9</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/3d-touch-ios9</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music I&#39;m Currently Enjoying</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve currently found myself listening to a strange mix of stuff now. However, here’s some new things I’m listening to. (I say new, new to me…)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All links direct you to Apple Music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lauren-aquilina&quot;&gt;Lauren Aquilina&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This beautiful &amp;amp; beautifully voiced soul has a new EP out. If you know me, you’ll know I love her anyway. But either way - the new EP is called ‘Ocean’ and is the newest single for her debut album which is coming…….soon……ish…..!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has a B-Side (who even does B-Sides anymore?!) called ‘Low’ which is just as beautiful. Another track called ‘Out Of Our Depth’ and three remixes, including a remix of ‘Ocean’ by Arty! Oooh! Arty farty!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go check out her god-damned EP on &lt;a href=&quot;https://itun.es/gb/jGYZ9&quot;&gt;Apple Music&lt;/a&gt; and if you love it just as much as I do, hit that buy button!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-staves&quot;&gt;The Staves&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am so damn slow at finding these beauts. They’ve recently supported Florence &amp;amp; The Machine on her last tour which is where I fell in love with them. Don’t ask me why I was at a Florence gig… though I will admit it was awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway… Another softy softy kinda band. But beautiful and chilling. ‘Blood I Bled’, ‘No Me, No You, No More’, ‘Let Me Down’ and ‘Make It Holy’ being my 4 fave tracks from their latest album ‘If I Was’. &lt;a href=&quot;https://itun.es/gb/02MS3&quot;&gt;Check it out!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;darude&quot;&gt;DaRude&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nope, I’m not trolling. He is indeed alive and has a brand new album called ‘Moments’ which is &lt;em&gt;awesome&lt;/em&gt;!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first track however, is a troll. It literally has about 50 ‘Sandstorm’ elements. But it’s a brilliant track and the album is wonderful. Get yer glowsticks out and &lt;a href=&quot;https://itun.es/gb/Fcoe9&quot;&gt;play it loud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;honorable-mention--gammer---im-old-now-wtf-happened&quot;&gt;Honorable Mention | Gammer - “I’m Old Now… WTF Happened?”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This album is full of classic amazing wonderful Gammer tunes. From back in the day all the way to now. Some of his best work is on here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Likewise, some of his best collaborations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a UK Hardcore fan, you will already have this. If you don’t, you should! And if you’re not, you should still give it a try!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://musicmondays.databeats.com/cd/mmcd011&quot;&gt;You can purchase the album from Music Mondays. Enjoy!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, there’s some insight into what I’m listening to right now…
Is there something I should be listening to? Hit me up on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/danbennett&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 23:32:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/music-im-currently-enjoying</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/music-im-currently-enjoying</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here&#39;s my problem with today&#39;s music</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In reference to &lt;a href=&quot;http://nypost.com/2015/10/04/your-favorite-song-on-the-radio-was-probably-written-by-these-two/&quot;&gt;this NYPost Article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;does-anyone-write-their-own-music-anymore&quot;&gt;Does anyone write their own music anymore?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of all the popular massive hits in the UK and America, how many of them are written by the artist themselves? Just that artist. No one else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve always thought it was rare to see an artist do that, which is one of the reasons I love new up and coming artists. Because at least they made the effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reading that article shows how sad a state pop music is in right now. Grand for the song writers, mind…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dont’t get me wrong. There’s nothing wrong with writing a song for someone else to sing because maybe you can’t or doesn’t interest you. But when it turns into a fucking factory, that is taking the piss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“For Rihanna, “A-list producers and topliners [the term for vocal melody writers] were summoned to Los Angeles for two weeks and installed in studios around the city,” creating what Seabrook calls “a pop-up hit factory.””&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So instead of Rihanna going “I’m going to write an album”, a &lt;em&gt;factory&lt;/em&gt; was made in which people write a bunch of songs, throw them around and the best of the bunch are then hers? eh?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Rihanna’s next album, “Rated R,” was a commercial and critical success, and its only No. 1, “Rude Boy,” emerged from the LA camp sessions. The song is credited to five different writers(if we count the two-man Stargate team as one entity), including Dean, who wrote the hooks; Rihanna herself, who wrote the bridge with Makeba Riddick; and Stargate and Rob Swire, who created the beats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 people wrote “Rude Boy”. 5 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you heard Rude Boy? If not, you don’t even need to. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/rihanna/rudeboy.html&quot;&gt;Lyrics&lt;/a&gt; themselves speak for my disgust. The longest line is 5 words!!!! That’s one word per person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I suppose to Rihanna’s credit, after being beaten by Chris Brown she probably struggled to think, so the fact she wrote the bridge is amazing… /s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Stargate and Dean would become frequent collaborators, with hits such as Katy Perry’s “Firework” on their résumé.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even Katy Perry couldn’t come up with lyrics such as “Do you ever feel like a plastic bag”?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Martin has played a pivotal role in Katy Perry’s career, co-writing and/or producing hits including “I Kissed a Girl,” “California Gurls,” and “Teenage Dream.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Katy didn’t write anything. Did she do anything? At all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;His three most recent No. 1 songs came from Taylor Swift’s blockbuster release, “1989” — “Shake It Off,” “Blank Space” and “Bad Blood.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHAT?! Even the beloved Taylor Swift, who I often thought of as genuine, doesn’t write all her own shit? Agh!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;once-you-succeed-you-no-longer-need-to-bother&quot;&gt;Once you succeed, you no longer need to bother&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s funny in a way. There are people out there who write their own music, produce their own songs and some of them write the best piece of fucking music imaginable. Yet they still have a job just to be able to pay for them to do the thing they love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What? Once you’ve had a hit are you no longer required to try?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, writing an album can take a long time. But it’s meant to. It’s a craft and an art that has to go through a process that involves sweat and tears. It’s should not be a case of some one going “Here’s 18 songs, we record tomorrow and the album is released next month”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where are the real musicians? The ones that, when they sing a song they sing it because they wrote it and it means something to them and comes from the heart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, they’re too busy struggling to get noticed because they don’t have people throwing deals at them so money can be made… and that’s a rant for another day…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 00:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/everything-about-todays-music-sucks</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/everything-about-todays-music-sucks</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple Watch and Me.</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-most-expensive-watch-ive-ever-bought&quot;&gt;The most expensive watch I’ve ever bought…&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s weird. I grew up hating watches or infact anything on my wrist. It always bugged me. Bracelets, watches, those stupid paper bands you get at gigs (OK those I still hate. Fabric ones are the best)…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this year I chose to get a Fitbit Flex. I wanted something that was accurate for step counting and I could just keep on. It would just be part of my life, not interupt it in any way. And it was great. I found myself walking more, forcing myself to take walks at lunch during work…
But then it died. And so I decided to get an Apple Watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was always considering an Apple Watch. And infact, I was fighting myself to stop me buying one. But once my FItbit died, I started considering it more. And my final choice was “Try it for 14 days. If I don’t like it within those two weeks, I can get a refund”… So I got my card out and bought one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the 32mm Apple Watch Sport. The cheapest of the bunch. And the silver one. The 32mm was a good shout, fits perfectly on me. The other was just far too big!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;watchos2&quot;&gt;WatchOS2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first started, WatchOS2 was already available for developers. So right away I installed it and got the benefits of some of the features. But my main thing I love about it is that it’s kept me active and actually hasn’t been as in the way as I expected. In fact, it’s been more useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nightstand function in WatchOS2 is brilliant for those of us that don’t have an alarm clock. I do now have an alarm clock, because I really wanted to listen to The Chris Moyles Show on Radio X in the mornings…. but the clock on that is lit up so bright it’s annoying. So I still use the watches clock!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;walk-fat-boy&quot;&gt;Walk, fat boy.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main way to keep fit is just walking. I like walking. I also don’t walk normal speed, I walk slightly faster than everyone (or incredibly fast if I’m in a shopping centre. Bugger me people walk so bloody slow!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The watch would monitor this, give me silly awards for doing so. It’s nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also forces me to try take more breaks during work. “Stand up for a minute every hour” is the recommendation. Now, that’s difficult to do because sometimes I just far too busy to do that. But where possible, I do. And I think it’s helped my productivity a lot. Maybe it’s in the mind I don’t know… but it has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also quite interesting to find out just how much I’ve done in a day. Some days I’ll be active but feel like I’ve done nothing. The Activity app reminds me that actually, there’s a very good reason why my legs are aching…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notifications&quot;&gt;Notifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my big concern. Would I get frustrated at being notified about everything when I can easily ignore them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, you can choose what you get notified by. And you can customise the notifications so they are different to your phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your phone notifications will always appear if they do not have a WatchOS equiv. But normally these are minor things that I don’t pay attention to anyway so I’ve just ended up turning them off so they only appear in Notification Centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For other notifications, such as Tweets, Messages, Facebook, Email… I have them customized so it gives me a little tap and if I want to look at it I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The slight downside, is the tap for Messages is a lot less than the tap for Tweets. So Messages I seem to miss more, but actually I care more about Messages. If I get a text, I want to at least glance at it. But I find I seem to occasionally not realise I’ve been tapped. That needs to be changed…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for the most part, I’ve worked out what I don’t need to be notified about and I can turn them off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take email. If it’s an email that comes through I can easily Archive it from the notification, or just put my wrist down and leave it for later.
Same for Messages. If it’s a message I can easily reply to with a word or an answer to a question, I’ll do that right from my watch. If it requires more attention then I can leave it for a bit and I’ve set it to remind me up to 3 times. If I’m too busy, it’ll just wait until I can pick my phone up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said though, if you do respond from your phone, the answers do come across a bit rude. I’d advise thinking of redoing them to suit the way you talk to everyone. Sometimes saying just “Yes” will make people think something is wrong. Nothing is wrong, I’m just multitasking like a mad man!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;games&quot;&gt;Games&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a few games for the Watch, but I’ve not really bothered with them. It’s not a gaming device…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trivia Crack is good - well - craic… But meh. Games stick to the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;strap-on-strap-off&quot;&gt;Strap on! Strap off!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch straps are… quite frankly, overpriced. Massively. So I’ve looked a lot into Third Party ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a nice third party Leather Loop strap. It’s pretty close to the official, except if you look closely it doesn’t fully match. Now normally, this’ll bug me. But for the price - not so much…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried the Milanese Mesh strap but found it would always pick at my hairs on my arms. so I’ve stuck with the Leather Loop. If I were out in the sun and knew I would be sweaty, I’d go back to the official Sport strap that came with my watch. But for now, the Leather Loop wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sleep-tracking&quot;&gt;Sleep Tracking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the things I loved about my Fitbit Flex was it’d monitor my sleep. The Apple Watch can do that, there are apps that do this. However, that requires you to wear it… yet I use it in the day, so the battery would die whilst I’m asleep…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are ways you can do it, if you change your behaviour. However - that’s not possible for me. So I’m no longer tracking my sleep which seems a bit anti-monitor-health-constantly-you-lazy-bastard-y.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;battery&quot;&gt;Battery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch is the kind of watch you wear in the day and take it off when you sleep. So, a typical watch really. Except when you take it off to sleep, you charge it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve not had any issue with the battery running low in the day (apart from a bug during WatchOS2 Beta’s…). I normally take it off charge around 8:15am and I put it back on charge at around 23:00… Normally there’s still ~50% battery left!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In heavy use (lots of walking, for example) this can get lower, but I’ve only really got it to the 30% mark. The only time I’ve really used the Power Reserve mode is  when I pretty much showing it off all day and playing with it. Once you get over the “OOOHHH SHINY SHINY” moments, it’s grand. Quite frankly - battery is a non-issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;worth-it&quot;&gt;Worth it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always, the price of Apple products is never really &lt;em&gt;worth it&lt;/em&gt;. But at the same time, you are paying for a premium made product. And actually, some watches that do less than the Apple Watch cost over £1000!! So in a way, it’s a bargain!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re into looking at keeping fit and you’re always active on your phone - I say go for it. This’ll help with both and actually get some of your social life back when you’re out at events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need a new watch - Just buy a watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;overall&quot;&gt;Overall…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m loving it. It’s just a nice watch that lets me know if I’ve been a good boy or a lazy sod. I can keep an eye on the important stuff and leave the non-vital stuff to when I can use my phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only downside? I wish I got the Space Grey version…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 22:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/apple-watch-for-me</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/apple-watch-for-me</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Early iPhone Reviews are Pointless...</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;how-can-you-review-something-after-a-day&quot;&gt;How can you review something after a day?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A day is not enough time to spend with the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every device is different, internally or externally. iPhone or Android.
When you get a new device, you have to learn it. Spend some time with it and see if it still suits the way you work… You cannot do this after one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially with the iPhone 6s/6s Plus. It has a new feature that drastically changes how you work. You cannot see if this fits in your life after one day (or some, even less). It’s stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking of buying the new iPhone, or any new device that has just been released - wait for a week or so. Give people time to make their actual thoughts concrete and see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now granted, another persons opinion won’t be the same as yours. But it’ll help you swing your direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last thing you want to do is spend over £600 and regret it, because it doesn’t fit your lifestyle and how you use the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the reviewers… A quick overview at the start is grand. But a review is not possible after a day unless you’re incredibly closed minded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Likewise, I’ll be posting a little overview at some point on my iPhone 6s. I should also do that about my Apple Watch…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/early-iphone-reviews-are-pointless</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/early-iphone-reviews-are-pointless</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iOS 9 slow after upgrade?</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;give-it-up-to-24-hours&quot;&gt;Give it up to 24 hours…&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know, it sounds a bit silly. But on most iOS major release, a lot will update, migrate, and index in the background.
This means Battery and Performance will take a temporary hit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just give it some time. And if need be, use the new “Low Power” mode to try and save some power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d always advise to update at night. Once the update has worked, leave it plugged in and go to bed. Most the time, it’s finished by the time you wake up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 10:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/ios9-slow-wait-24-hours</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/ios9-slow-wait-24-hours</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ellie Goulding’s announced details of her 22-track (!) ‘Delirium’ album</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.popjustice.com/thenews/ellie-gouldings-announced-details-of-her-22-track-delirium-album/138398/&quot;&gt;RE: Popjustice Article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited to hear this. I’ve heard it’s big, but also epic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But will it beat Album 1 (well, actually, ‘Bright Lights’), which is and probably always will be my anthem album of hers?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/ellie-goulding-delirium-announced</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/ellie-goulding-delirium-announced</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook is considering the addition of a &#39;Dislike&#39; button</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;why&quot;&gt;Why?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, they’ve been saying that for a long time now…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, why the hell do people want a “Dislike” button on Facebook?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; something on Facebook, don’t press the like button!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Like&lt;/em&gt; button is there for spreading positivity. If you agree something or like something, you press it and show that. It saves writing “me too!” or “+1”…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But a &lt;em&gt;Dislike&lt;/em&gt; button is just about negativity. Why is negativity something people want to share?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of the problems with YouTube. They have a &lt;em&gt;Dislike&lt;/em&gt; button and people get upset by it’s numbers or attack other YouTubers by getting their videos purposely disliked…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Positivity is better than Negativity and is something that should be shared and encouraged. Nowadays more than ever, it seems…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 14:26:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/facebook-is-considering-a-dislike-button</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/facebook-is-considering-a-dislike-button</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Prefer iOS over Android</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;and-why-the-whole-debate-is-dumb&quot;&gt;And why the whole debate is dumb…&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s strange how even to this day, the iOS vs Android debate continues…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyday there is some sort of debate going on about why iOS is better than Android or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, why? Why does it matter what device someone is using? And why do you care?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why can’t you just let them make up their own mind?
&amp;gt;”I’m saving them money”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In your opinion. For them it might turn to be a costly mistake because what you think is best turns out not best for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“People on iOS/Android are stupid”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who are you to state the mental capacity of another person?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Don’t join the iSheep”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using a device you’re comfortable with doesn’t mean you’re a “sheep” or a “fanboy”. Likewise, you cannot call someone a “fanboy” if it’s their first device or if they simply don’t care…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“You can do more on iOS/Android”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can do the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“You can customize more on iOS/Android”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They both have their own ways of customization. It’s up to the user how much they want to customize it and whether the available options work for them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 18:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/why-i-prefer-ios-over-android</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/why-i-prefer-ios-over-android</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has &#39;Verification&#39; lost it&#39;s meaning?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a post I put on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/dan-bennett/has-verification-lost-it-s-meaning-43693f0bd9df&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; page which I am reblogging here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-2.medium.com/max/800/1*bH2kwle04letJEDVLDjtnA.png&quot; alt=&quot;verification&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn’t it strange, how one simple tick can make a person seem above everyone else?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get why it’s used. It’s to help establish the real “Celebrities” from the parody/fake accounts. But the first statement that explains what the Verified Badge is makes it sound like everyone should be able to get the tick if they can prove they are who they say they are&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Any account with a blue verified badge on their Twitter profile is a verified account.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great! Let me access it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Verification is currently used to establish authenticity of identities of key individuals and brands on Twitter.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh — so I’m not famous enough?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Please note that follower count is not a factor in determining whether an account meets our criteria for verification.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh — so it’s about how famous I am in real life? No, that can’t be right. Upcoming artists (as an example) seem to get verified quite quickly before even having their first big hit…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We concentrate on highly sought users in music, acting, fashion, government, politics, religion, journalism, media, sports, business and other key interest areas.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s strange. To get a verification tick you have to be a well known somebody in the world. Yet getting that verification tick helps you get more well known. So surely it’s a good idea to let people who are independent in these areas get a tick, too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a strange conversation once, where someone found my music from Soundcloud and wanted to find me on Twitter. They tweeted me asking if this Soundcloud was me and I responded yes. They then said they weren’t sure because I don’t have a tick…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I can’t have a tick because I’m not famous or signed. Yet people may not be finding me fully because I don’t have a tick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I make it quite easy for everyone anyway. I use my real name for everything and no matter what genre I make music wise. Yet somehow, there’s still a chance that someone will see my name think “That’s not him, he’s not got a tick”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a real person guys and girls. Honest!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of this, what seems to be happening recently is that everyone wants the tick and get upset when one person does and they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YouTube for example is another place that has started doing Verified Accounts. Which is great! But… there’s no real outline to who can get it or how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Why do you have a tick when you have less subs than me???”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s getting a bit silly, really. With social media being so engrained in everyone’s lives now. Surely it’s better to allow everyone to have the chance and be verified? Whether they’re an artist, YouTuber, gamer, blogger, writer, or even generic Joe from number 18 down the road…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The separation between online and offline lives is narrower than ever…Scary. But awesome at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/has-verification-lost-its-meaning</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/has-verification-lost-its-meaning</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple Pencil: They had to eventually...</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;it-was-only-a-matter-of-time&quot;&gt;It was only a matter of time…&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple have announced the Apple Pencil, which is their own Stylus for the newer, bloody big, iPad Pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter was full of storm, mostly quoting old Steve Jobs during the original iPhone announcement stating;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Who wants a stylus?” … “You have to get ‘em, put ‘em away, you lose ‘em. Yuck! Nobody wants a stylus. So let’s not use a stylus.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yes, for the iPhone this is correct. And for the most part, this was correct for the iPad.
But as more people were using the iPad, finding ways to incorporate it into their lives, it became obvious a stylus can actually be useful…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;not-just-any-stylus&quot;&gt;Not just any Stylus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Apple to include a stylus, they had to make it work properly. This is the Apple way. They don’t just take something that already exists. They completely rebuild it into something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main reason the stylus has only come from Apple now, is because it’s now at a point (pun intended?) where they have developed the technology to make it work with almost zero latency for drawing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was the main problem with a stylus. It’s slower. With a finger you don’t mind it, you mostly tap. You hardly even notice it. But once you start typing, or drawing, the latency was obvious and a constant battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ipad-pro-only-for-now&quot;&gt;iPad Pro Only… For now.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only reason the Apple Pencil only works for the iPad Pro is because, in true Apple fashion, the Pencil and the iPad talk to each other. iPad Pro screen refresh rate is increased dramatically for using the Pencil to help with the latency. Likewise, they both have to know and talk to each other as quick as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both the iPad and Pencil have to work together to make it work properly. This is not something that was possible with a 3rd party stylus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, for a long time now you can buy a stylus that allows for pressure and sends that data via Bluetooth, but the delay is still there and it’s painful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now? That pain has gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s only a matter of time until the iPad Air and iPad Mini are refreshed to work with the Apple Pencil. And hopefully, that time isn’t too far away…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 13:25:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/apple-pencil-they-had-to-eventually</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/apple-pencil-they-had-to-eventually</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I need a logo...</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-is-thinking-of-a-logo-so-hard&quot;&gt;Why is thinking of a logo so hard?!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A logo is your identity. Your visual representation that people will see before they realize who they’re looking at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gives a lot of information about you. But how can I get it right?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one I’ve currently got &lt;img src=&quot;http://dan-bennett.me/assets/images/logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt; is, let’s be honest… a bit crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had this idea of it being audio related. using my initials in a way to also mean decibel (&lt;em&gt;cringe&lt;/em&gt;) and kind of sound waves coming out the sides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other trouble is the colors… It needs to stand out, be unique… But also look good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blue and Orange are my favorite colors. But - they just don’t sit right. Or at least, not in the way they are in the logo right now…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gah! All it really says is about me is “Try hard, but not quite a thing”. Which may be more accurate than I realize…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 12:34:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/i-need-a-logo</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/i-need-a-logo</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new start!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome&quot;&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it’s that time again where I decide I need to rebuild this website and get cracking with posting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve decided that the theme is, quite simply, “The Brain Dump”.
I want a place that I can just use to post my thoughts on particular articles or subjects, as well as the ability to give informational posts. So hopefully this will be it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to keep it simple looking. Kind of “Medium”-esqe…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;goodbye-wordpress&quot;&gt;Goodbye, Wordpress!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve decided I’ve had enough of Wordpress and it’s complete pain in the arseness. It was bloated, slow, painful to hack to how I want it and… gah. I just got fed up.
I was never happy with how it looked or ran. Probably mostly because I’m not a designer, to be fair…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;welcome-jekyll&quot;&gt;Welcome, Jekyll!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a wonderful little blogging system which relies on Markdown for it’s posts. Each post is just a simple text file. No more databases!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other plus I’ve found about Jekyll is it’s very easy for me to develop and draft stuff, without it affecting the live site!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking of moving from Wordpress, or would like to use something that requires more backend tinkering and less stumbling through awful UI/UX - then &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is for you!
(Oh - and it’s Open Source!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-theme-gaya&quot;&gt;The theme? Gaya!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sites look and feel is based on an open source template called ‘&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/gayanvirajith/gaya&quot;&gt;Gaya&lt;/a&gt;’. Obviously, it’s by this time completely different. But there you go! It was the closest beginning template to what I wanted to achieve in my mind!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So… Let’s see what happens with this. Do I fail and stumble? Or do I come out shining? There’s only one way to find out …&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 11:41:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://dan-bennett.me/a-new-start</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dan-bennett.me/a-new-start</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
